&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么让我们谈谈这个关于课堂的最后一次练习。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's talk about this final exercise on classes.
记住，我们将这个名称空间对象转换为一个类。
Remember, we were turning this name space object into a class.
这些方法中的大多数机制将是完全相同的，
Most of the mechanisms inside of these methods are gonna be exactly the same,
这是个好消息。
which is the good news.
您不必更改其中的很多代码，但是
You didn't have to change a lot of the code inside of it, but
我们本质上是在改变围绕它的组织。
we're essentially changing the organization around it.
所以，与其拥有一个容纳这些东西的物体，
So rather than having an object that holds these things,
我们将会有一堂课，我们会称之为“班级工作坊”。
we're gonna have a class, and we're gonna call that class Workshop.
而不是有属性在上面，
And instead of having properties on it,
我们必须有一个构造函数来设置它们。
we're gonna have to have a constructor that sets those up.
所以我们将创建一个构造函数
So we'll make a constructor that says
this.currentEnrollment等于空数组，并且
this.currentEnrollment equals the empty array and
this.StudentRecords等于空数组。
this.studentRecords equals the empty array.
现在，所有其余的方法都是我们的类定义中的方法，所以
Now all the rest of these are just methods now inside of our class definition so
我们可以去掉那些逗号。
we can remove those commas.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，所有这些都应该保持不变
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, so all of those should stand without any changes
因为它们都正确地处理了我们实例的这个上下文。
because they are all properly handling this context of our instance.
但自述文件提到了一件小事，
But there was one little thing with the Readme mention,
那就是拉出不知道的功能，并且
which was to pull out the functions that are not this aware, and
其中有两个，sortByName和printRecord。
there are two of them, the sortByName and the printRecord.
这两个不是，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这个意识，
These two are not, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: This aware,
而且它们与工作坊并没有什么特别的关系。
and they're not really related to the Workshop specifically.
所以我们要把他们放在帮手家长班。
And so we're gonna put them in a Helpers parent class.
Helpers父类不需要构造函数。
That Helpers parent class doesn't need a constructor.
但是现在我们定义了一个父类，它确实意味着一些细微的差别，这
But now that we're defining a parent class, it does mean a little nuance, which
我们必须确保从我们的子构造函数调用super。
is that we're gonna have to make sure to call super from our child constructor.
如果没有定义子构造函数，它会自动定义。
If you don't define a child constructor, it automatically does.
但如果创建子构造函数，则必须调用super
But if you make a child constructor, you have to call super
调用父构造函数，您必须首先这样做。
to invoke the parent constructor, and you have to do it first.
这样就有一个为您构建的this对象。
So that there is a this object that has been constructed for you.
好的，现在我们需要添加Extensions子句，Extensions Helpers。
Okay, so now we need to add the extends clause, extends Helpers.
然后我们应该有的唯一的另一个改变
And then the only other change that we should have
要做的是我们需要实例化deep JS
to make is that we need to instantiate the deepJS
通过调用Deep JS来创建对象等于新工作坊。
object by calling deepJS equals new Workshop.
如果我没有遗漏什么，希望这段代码现在应该可以工作了。
And if I didn't miss something, hopefully this code should now work.
让我们切换到这个环境，让我们运行这段代码，看看我们得到了什么。
Let's switch over to this environments and let's run this code and see what we got.
这是我们的输出。
And there's our output.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以这是我们基于类的定义，而不是使用
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So there's our class-based definition rather than using
命名空间。
a name space.
这是我们车间管理的基于类的定义。
It's our class-based definition for our Workshop management.
关于使用类语法组织此代码的问题？
Questions about using the class syntax to organize this code?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：当您从工作坊创建Deep JS时，是否使用了new？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Did you use new when you created deepJS from Workshop?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，我们在处理构造函数时必须使用new。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yep, and we have to use new when we're dealing with a constructor.
例如，当定义工作坊是模块工厂时，
For example, when define Workshop was a module factory,
这只是一个常规函数，所以我们只调用它。
that's just a regular function so we just called it.
但由于这是一个类构造函数，
But since this is a class constructor,
我们实际上需要用一个新的关键字来调用它，就像普通的类一样。
we actually need to invoke it with a new keyword like you would a normal class.